Register of the Stanford University Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies Collection, 1954-1965
Hoover Institution Archives
- April 1963
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador (Box 558.)
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (6 envelopes, one containing Excelsior Apr. 20-30) (Box 559.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes) (Box 560.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 561.)
  - Puerto Rico, (4 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes) (Box 562.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (7 envelopes) (Box 563.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana
  - British Honduras, (2 envelopes) (Box 564.)
  - Jamaica
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
  - International (Box 565.)
- May 1963
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 565.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama (Box 566.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (5 envelopes)
  - Colombia (Box 567.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 568.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (4 envelopes) (Box 569.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (contains Excelsior May 1-10)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 570.)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 571.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama, (2 envelopes) (Box 572.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (5 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 573.)
  - Puerto Rico, (4 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 574.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (5 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 575.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 576.)
  - British Guiana (Box 577.)
  - British Honduras
  - French West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - Netherlands West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies (3 envelopes, one including other Islands)
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- June 1963
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 578.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 579.)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 580.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador (Box 581.)
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 582.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 583.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (5 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 584.)
  - Puerto Rico, (5 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain (Box 585.)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 586.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 587.)
  - West Indies, British Honduras, British Guiana, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes) (Box 588.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- July 1963
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 589.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama (Box 590.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 591.)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 592.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes) (Box 593.)
  - El Salvador
  - Haiti
  - Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 594.)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 595.)
  - Mexico (Box 596.)
  - Nicaragua, (3 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (2 envelopes, one containing pictures of Pres. Belaunde's cabinet members)
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 597.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 598.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes) (Box 599.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (6 envelopes) (Box 600.)
  - Venezuela (Box 601.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (4 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes) (Box 602.)
- August 1963
  - Argentina (Box 602.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes) (Box 603.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 604.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 605.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (5 envelopes including one on Economics, one on Labor and Utilities, one on Religion and one on Politics) (Box 606.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Haiti, (3 envelopes) (Box 607.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 608.)
  - Nicaragua, (3 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay (Box 609.)
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 610.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (Box 611.)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 612.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 613.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes) (Box 614.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (5 envelopes)
- September 1963
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 615.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama (Box 616.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 617.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 618.)
  - Dominican Republic, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes) (Box 619.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (3 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 620.)
  - Nicaragua (Box 621.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 622.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (5 envelopes) (Box 623.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 624.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 625.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (4 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands Antilles and Surinam
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (5 envelopes) (Box 626.)
- October 1963
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 627.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 628.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes) (Box 629.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 630.)
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (4 envelopes) (Box 631.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Slavador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 632.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama (Box 633.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (4 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rica, (4 envelopes) (Box 634.)
  - Spain (Box 635.)
  - Uruguay, (7 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (6 envelopes) (Box 636.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 637.)
  - Venezuela (Box 638.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (5 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - Netherlands Antilles and Surinan
  - International
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 639.)
- November 1963
  - Bolivia (Box 639.)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 640.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 641.)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (3 envelopes including Foreign Affairs, Health, Press, and Interior Politics)
  - Dominican Republic (3 envelopes including Interior Politics, Labor and Economics of Agriculture) (Box 642.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 643.)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 644.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (4 envelopes) (Box 645.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Puerto Rico, (4 envelopes) (Box 646.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (11 envelopes, including a special on Pres. Kennedy's Assassination) (Box 647.)
  - Venezuela, (6 envelopes) (Box 648.)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 649.)
  - British West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - British West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras (Box 650.)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 651.)
- December 1963
  - Argentina (also contains 1962 material) (Box 651.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 652.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 653.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (7 envelopes, including Economics, Internal Affairs)
  - Dominican Repubilc (Box 654.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 655.)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 656.)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 657.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (6 envelopes) (Box 658.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 659.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 660.)
  - Uruguay, (8 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (Box 661.)
  - Venezuela, (6 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes and loose papers) (Box 662.)
  - Venezuela (Box 663.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- January 1964
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes) (Box 663.)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes) (Box 664.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes) (Box 665.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 666.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador (Box 667.)
  - El Salvador
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 668.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (10 envelopes) (Box 669.)
  - Paraguay, (2 envelopes) (Box 670.)
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 671.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (7 envelopes) (Box 672.)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 673.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes) (Box 674.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- February 1964
  - Bolivia (Box 675.)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (5 envelopes) (Box 676.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 677.)
  - Cuba (Box 678.)
  - Dominican Republic, (7 envelopes)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti (Box 679.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 680.)
  - Nicaragua (Box 681.)
  - Panama, (17 envelopes)
  - Panama, (11 envelopes) (Box 682.)
  - Panama, (4 envelopes) (Box 683.)
  - Paraguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 684.)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain, (3 envelopes) (Box 685.)
  - Uruguay, (9 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (8 envelopes) (Box 686.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes) (Box 687.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
  - International (Box 688.)
- March 1964
  - Bolivia (Box 688.)
  - Brazil, (7 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (11 envelopes) (Box 689.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes) (Box 690.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (9 envelopes) (Box 691.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 692.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes) (Box 693.)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 694.)
  - Mexico (Box 695.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Paraguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Peru (Box 696.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 697.)
  - Spain, (3 envelopes) (Box 698.)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 699.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 700.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 701.)
- April 1964
  - Bolivia (Box 701.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (8 envelopes) (Box 702.)
  - Brazil, (7 envelopes) (Box 703.)
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes) (Box 704.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 705.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes) (Box 706.)
  - Dominican Republic, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes) (Box 707.)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti (2 envelopes, one April - May)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (7 envelopes) (Box 708.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (7 envelopes) (Box 709.)
  - Paraguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (4 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes) (Box 710.)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain, (5 envelopes) (Box 711.)
  - Uruguay, (9 envelopes) (Box 712.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 713.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 714.)
- May 1964
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes) (Box 714.)
  - Brazil, (7 envelopes) (Box 715.)
  - Central America and Panama (Box 716.)
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (11 envelopes) (Box 717.)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 718.)
  - Dominican Republic, (6 envelopes)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes) (Box 719.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (6 envelopes) (Box 720.)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 721.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (10 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 722.)
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 723.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 724.)
  - Uruguay, (5 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 725.)
  - Venezuela, (9 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 726.)
  - West Indies, British, Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 727.)
- June 1964
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes) (Box 727.)
  - Brazil, (6 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes) (Box 728.)
  - Central America, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (7 envelopes) (Box 729.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (4 envelopes) (Box 730.)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 731.)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 732.)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 733.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (2 envelopes) (Box 734.)
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 735.)
  - Uruguay, (7 envelopes) (Box 736.)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 737.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 738.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
  - International, (7 envelopes) (Box 739.)
- July 1964
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes) (Box 739.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (9 envelopes) (Box 740.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (3 envelopes) (Box 741.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Colombia (Box 742.)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes) (Box 743.)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (5 envelopes) one being July - August (Box 744.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru (Box 745.)
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 746.)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 747.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 748.)
  - Jamaica, Trinidad, Tobago, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- August 1964
  - Argentina (Box 749.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (7 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes) (Box 750.)
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 751.)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (2 envelopes, including one in Politics)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador, (2 envelopes) (Box 752.)
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua (Box 753.)
  - Panama, (3 envelopes)
  - Peru, (4 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal (Box 754.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes) (Box 755.)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 756.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies (August - December)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- September 1964
  - Argentina (Box 757.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (8 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes) (Box 758.)
  - Chile, (6 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes) (Box 759.)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 760.)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador, (3 envelopes)
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 761.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (5 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes) (Box 762.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (Box 763.)
  - Venezuela, (7 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana
  - West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- October 1964
  - Argentina (Box 764.)
  - Bolivia, (4 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (6 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 765.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia (2 envelopes, including one September - October)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes) (Box 766.)
  - Ecuador, (4 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Haiti
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay (October - December)
  - Peru
  - Peru, (2 envelopes) (Box 767.)
  - Puerto Rico, (7 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 768.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes)
  - Netherlands West Indies
- November 1964
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes) (Box 768.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes) (Box 769.)
  - Chile
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala (October - November)
  - Haiti
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 770.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes)
  - Netherlands West Indies
- December 1964
  - Bolivia (November - December) (Box 770.)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba (December 1964 - January 1965)
  - Cuba (Box 771.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Peru (November 1964 - January 1965)
  - Puerto Rico (November 1964 - January 1965)
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - French West Indies
- Miscellaneous
  - Events of October 1961 issued December 1961 (Box 772.)
  - Events of November 1961 pub. January 1962
  - Events of December 1961 issued February 1962
  - Events of January 1962 issued March 1962
  - Political
  - Extra copies - descriptions of indexing
  - Subject index supplement foreign relations - in 1961
  - Events of April 1961 issued June
  - Extra copy of report for present name indexing (Box 773.)
  - May 1961 issued June 1961
  - June 1961 issued August 1961
  - Events of July 1961 issued September
  - Events of August 1961 published October
  - Events of September published November
  - Argentina (1964)
  - Mexico (4 envelopes, one being August 1964, one being September 1964, and two being October 1964) (Box 774.)
  - Mexico, (6 envelopes) (Box 775.)
  - Paraguay
  - Mexico (6 envelopes, May - November 1964) (Box 776.)
  - Nicaragua (2 envelopes, 1 October 1964, 1 November 1964)
  - Spain
  - Cuba 1960-1967 general file, (3 envelopes) (Box 777.)
  - Guatemala
  - Hispanic American Report Cuttings from International Files
  - Hispanic American Report Manual - Caribbean (notebook)
  - Venezuela - Index to Material of - (black notebook)